嘿，你们帮我一臂之力了吗？
Hey you guys give me a hand will ya?
你觉得你到底在做什么，是吗？
What the hell do you think you're doing, huh?
咦？
Huh?
拿着它！
Hold it!
看它！
Watch it!
出去！ 出去！
Get out! Get out!
跑！ 跑！
Run! Run!
跑！ 好啦好啦！
Run! Come on, come on!
没有！ 你的儿子..
No! You son of a..
哦，我的上帝。
Oh my god.
雷切尔，这是丹。 第十洞。 发生了一起谋杀案 -
Rachel, this is Dan. Tenth hole. There's been a murder -
你最好快点把警察赶出去！
所有西区单位：在市政高尔夫球场可能4-51。 马上回应。
All West Side units: Possible 4-51 at municipal golf course.║Respond immediately.
you better get the cops out here, quick!
复制。  4-51在高尔夫球场。 我们走吧！
Copy. 4-51 at the golf course. Let's go!
拿枪。 关闭一个婊子的儿子！
Get the gun. Off the son of a bitch!
所有单位。 所有单位。 我们有10-20。
All units. All Units. We have a 10-20.
在西湖市政高尔夫球场。
At Western Lake municipal golf course.
谨慎行事。 我再说一遍：谨慎行事。 过度。
Proceed with caution. I repeat: Proceed with caution. Over.
10-4我们正在前进。
10-4 we're on our way.
他在那！ 保持你的火力。 我没有人能击中那台直升机。
There he is!║Hold your fire. I don't anyone to hit that chopper.
坚持下去，我会得到他的！
Hold on, I'll get him!
在这里打电话给护理人员！
Call the paramedics in here!
从水中取出这两个！
Get these two out of the water!
他必须在水中。 当心。
He must be in the water. Look out.
嘿这边！
Hey over here!
他去了！
There he goes!
你们快点！
You guys hurry up!
你们来这里吧..
You guys come on down here..
来吧，来吧 赶快！
Come on over here. Hurry up!
我有他。 我有他。 他就在这儿！
I've got him. I've got him. He's right here!
当心！
Look out!
得到了他！
Got him!
到底是怎么回事？
What's going on?
他去哪儿了？ 他到底去了哪里？
Where'd he go? Where the hell did he go?
他不只是在这里吗？
Weren't he just here?
该死的！
Damn!
他站在这儿..让我们找到这个家伙！ 来吧！
He was standing right here..║Let's find this dude! Come on!
扩散;传播开。 我们来找他！ 我们走吧。 来吧。
Spread out. Let's get him!║Let's go. Come on.
我他妈的'离开这里。 该死，留在一起的男人。
I'm fuckin' outta here. Dammit, stay together man.
♪我的心脏和灵魂都在发烧♪
♪ There's a fever running through my heart and soul ♪
♪因为有人带我回家而挨饿♪
♪ So hungry for someone to take me home ♪
♪爱咬♪
♪ Love Bites ♪
♪我可以在夜晚品尝它♪
♪ I can taste it in the night ♪
♪我需要一个情人♪
♪ I need a lover ♪
♪爱咬♪
♪ Love Bites ♪
♪我必须养活我的胃口♪
♪ I've got to feed my appetite ♪
♪找到我的情人♪
♪ Find me a lover ♪
♪我一直在等♪
♪ I've been waiting ♪
♪对于爱的比赛的罢工♪
♪ For the striking of the match of love ♪
♪有人会带我♪
♪ Someone who'll take me ♪
♪脱离我的脚和欲望的热度♪
♪ Off my feet and to the heat of desire ♪
♪我还能坚持多久？  ♪
♪ How much longer can I keep on holding on? ♪
♪有人来救我♪
♪ Someone come and rescue me ♪
♪我几乎走了♪
♪ I'm almost gone ♪
嘿! 你还好吗？
Hey! Are you alright?
你需要帮助吗？
Do you need any help?
天啊！
Oh god!
没有！
No!
[说日语]
[Speaking japanese]
你没有看到任何类型的武器？ 甚至没有枪或刀？
You didn't see any kind of a weapon?║Not even a gun or a knife?
不..可能在附近？
No..║Lying nearby maybe?
我告诉你了。 我找到他时他已经死了。
I told you. He was dead when I found him.
但你确定吗？
But are you sure?
我没有检查他。 我不是基督徒的护理人员。
I didn't examine him. I'm not a paramedic for christ sakes.
无论如何这是什么？
What is this anyway?
冷静。
Calm down.
现在，这名男子谋杀了一位非常重要的科学家 -
Now, this man murdered a very important scientist -
杀害保安，警察 -
killed security guards, police men -
我们对他一无所知。
and we know nothing about him.
给她一个休息中尉。
Give her a break lieutenant.
好的？
Alright?
是的，好的。
Yeah, OK.
看，莱德小姐，你现在可以走了。
Look, miss Ryder, you may go now.
你保持联系。
You keep in touch.
大忙的一天，对吧？
Rough day, huh?
是的，谢谢，但我不使用软饮料。
Yeah, thanks, but I don't use soft-drinks.
一些咖啡怎么样？
How about some coffee?
没有。
No.
威士忌酒？
Whiskey?
一个代基里酒？
A daiquiri?
抱歉。
Sorry.
比萨？
Pizza?
塔克？
Taco?
一些糖果怎么样？
How about some candy?
你还好吗？
Are you alright?
是的，我很好。 我只需要独自一人。
Yeah I'm OK. I just need to be alone.
我带你回家
Let me take you home.
没有！
No!
看，你说得好。 我不跟警察出去，好吗？
Look, you get this straight. I don't go out with cops, alright?
这个名字叫Secord。
The name is Secord.
比利塞多德。
Billy Secord.
我会联系你。
I'll be in touch.
哦，基督。
Oh christ.
上帝是她的美丽。
God is she beautiful.
不，不，不，不，不。
No, no, no, no, no.
你好？
Hello?
是的，她就在这里。
Yeah, she's right here.
是？
Yes?
你好。
Hi.
精细。
Fine.
对不起，我有健美操课。
Sorry, I've got an aerobics class.
不，我不会告诉你它在哪里。
No, I'm not gonna tell you where it's at.
嘿，看，你能解雇它吗？ 这不是卡片好吗？
Hey look, would you just lay off it buddy. It's just not in the cards alright?
你真是个朋友..
What a friend you are..
嘿克里斯蒂。
Hey Christie.
这到底是什么？
What the hell is this?
你有这个杀死警察或什么？
You got this to kill the cop with or something?
大多数人更喜欢你知道的枪支。
Most people prefer guns you know.
来吧我们走吧。 我们要迟到了。
Come on let's go. We're gonna be late.
一。 二。 三。 四。 踢。
One. Two. Three. Four. Kick.
一。 二。 三。 四。 让你的腿在那里。 来吧。
One. Two. Three. Four. Get your legs up there. Come on.
三。 四。 你做的很棒。
Three. Four. You're doing great.
使用那些武器。 是啊。 走。
Use those arms. Yeah. Go.
在左边。 二。 三。
And to the left. Two. Three.
你做得很好。 是啊。
You're doing real good. Yeah.
膝盖起来。 而且下来。 二。 三。
Knees up. And down. Two. Three.
四和伸展。 伸展。
Four and stretch. Stretch.
来吧你们让我们走吧。 伸展。
Come on you guys let's go. Stretch.
伸展。 二。 三。 四。
And stretch. Two. Three. Four.
现在很容易。 捻。 二。 用你的手臂。
Now easy. Twist. Two. Use your arms.
是啊。 继续走。 是啊。 充满活力的家伙。
Yeah. Keep moving. Yeah. Full of energy guys.
是啊。 继续。 二。
Yeah. Keep going. Two.
好。 你们准备好了吗？
OK. Are you guys ready?
是啊！ 是啊。
Yeah! Yeah.
双手向前。 和侧面。 侧。 向前。 去。
Hands forward. And Side. Side. Forward. And go.
来吧。 继续。 我们差不多完成了。 踢。 踢。
Come on. Keep going. We're almost finished. And kick. Kick.
踢。 二。 三。 现在我们正在尝试跑步。
Kick. Two. Three. Now we're trying running.
走。 快点。 走。 走。
Go. Faster. Go. Go.
走。 拜托你们吧。 快点。
Go. Come on you guys. Faster.
让它燃烧！
Make it burn!
拜托你们吧。 你在做什么？ 别现在停下来。 我们差不多完成了。
Come on you guys. What are you doing?║Don't stop now. We're almost finished.
来吧。 好极了。 你们做得很棒。 好的！
Come on. Yay. You guys are doing great. Alright!
好。 你好伙计。 走一点点。
OK. Good class you guys. Walk around a little bit.
伸展那些肌肉。
Stretch out those muscles.
在洗澡之前冷静下来。以后再见。
Cool down before you take shower. See you all later.
你不是要放弃了吗？
You're just not gonna quit are you?
我只是一个顽固的家伙。
I'm just a stubborn kind of guy.
不开玩笑。
No kidding.
嘿等一下。
Hey wait a minute.
你听说你找到的那个人是专业的日本刺客吗？
Did you hear that guy you found was a professional Japanese assassin?
你的意思是你一直都去我的健美操课，只是为了告诉我这件事？
You mean you went all the way to my aerobics class just to tell me that?
你仍然不会让事情变得简单吗？
You still won't make it easy will you?
哦。 那现在应该很容易吗？
Oh. So now it should be easy?
就这一次。 所以..
Just this once. So..
一些咖啡怎么样？
How about some coffee?
你知道咖啡对你的健康有害吗？
You know coffee is really bad for your health?
没有。哦不。
No. No. Oh no.
不，不，不，不。
No. No please, no.
请别打扰我。 请别打扰我。 没有。
Leave me alone. Leave me alone. No.
嘿!
Hey!
拜托你们吧。 现在让她走！
Come on you guys. Now let her go!
继续露西。 不要让他们吓唬你。
Go on Lucy. Don't let them scare you.
嘿，你以为你到底是谁？
Hey, who the hell you think you are?
我是那个告诉你让我离开的人。
I'm the one telling you to get out of my way.
或者也许我们只是为了拯救你的沙漠耶？
Or maybe we just save you for desert yeah?
你们真恶心！
You guys are disgusting!
好吧，对不起！
Well excuse me!
把它关掉！
Knock it off!
嘿，这是你的想法。
Hey it was your idea in the first place.
去死吧！
Go to hell!
是啊。 你看。 我们会成为朋友好吗？
Yeah. Hey look. We'll be friends alright?
我们洗个澡。 喝几杯啤酒..
We'll take a shower. Have a couple of beers..
把你的手从我身上移开！
Get your hands off of me!
来吧！
Come on!
你想要什么？
What do you want?
保持安静，移动你的屁股。 你被捕了。
Just keep quiet and move your butt. You're under arrest.
看。 如果你要预定我 然后预定我。
Look. If you're gonna book me. Then book me.
否则就不要打扰我了。
Otherwise just don't bother me anymore.
哦，我不会逮捕你。
Oh I'm not gonna arrest you.
我只是想带你回到我原来的邻居。
I just wanna take you back to my old neighborhood.
那里有一个人我想让你为我殴打。
There's a guy there I want you to beat up for me.
你会停车吗？
Would you stop the car?
哦，来吧。 我只是在取笑你。
Oh come on. I'm only teasing you.
停下车！
Stop the car!
看看科视我只是想帮忙。
Look Christie I'm only trying to help.
对于你对那些家伙的所作所为，你会受到指控。
You'd get charged for assault for what you did to those guys.
那是我的问题。
Well that's my problem.
而且我不需要任何帮助。
And I don't need any help.
特别是你，军官Secord。
Especially from you, officer Secord.
你懂。 我厌倦了听你怎么不喜欢警察。
You know. I am sick and tired of hearing about how you don't like cops.
因为我想告诉你一件事，想念Independence。
Because I wanna tell you something, miss Independence.
我喜欢当警察。
I like being a cop.
如果你不想和我一起出去，因为我是一名警察 -
And if you don't wanna go out with me just 'cause I'm a cop -
女士，然后和你一起去。
Then to hell with you, lady.
你现在可以离开了。
You can go now.
听..
Listen..
我的公寓里没有咖啡 -
I don't have any coffee in my apartment -
但我确实有一些V-8果汁。
But I do have some V-8 juice.
你想带我回家吗？
Would you like to take me home?
♪宝贝看看我♪
♪ Baby take a look at me ♪
♪有一些我必须知道的事情♪
♪ There's something that I've got to know ♪
♪你会和我一起冒险♪
♪ Are you gonna take a chance with me ♪
♪或只是一场停止和去的游戏♪
♪ Or just a game of stop and go ♪
♪你会让我进来♪
♪ Are you gonna let me in ♪
♪或者它会是一个孤独的夜晚♪
♪ Or is it gonna be a lonely night ♪
♪我们接近尾声♪
♪ Are we getting near the end ♪
♪或刚刚开始正确♪
♪ Or just starting up right ♪
♪宝贝看看我♪
♪ Baby take a look at me ♪
♪真的那么糟糕的脸♪
♪ Is it really that bad a face ♪
♪也许你有别人♪
♪ Maybe you've got someone else ♪
♪但也许我可以取代他的位置♪
♪ But maybe I could take his place ♪
♪我可以给它我最好的拍摄♪
♪ I could give it my best shot ♪
我喜欢你的睡衣。
I like your pajamas.
这是你在车上放的一个节目。
That was quite a show you put on in your car.
对不起。 我并不是故意生气。
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to get so angry.
那没问题。
That's OK.
当你生气时，你很性感。
You're very sexy when you get angry.
天啊。
Oh god.
克里斯蒂？
Christie?
你在做什么？
What are you doing?
没有。
Nothing.
我无法入睡。
I just couldn't sleep.
我做了一个噩梦所以我决定把一些衣服拿走。
I had a nightmare so I decided to put some clothes away.
神。 这很漂亮。
God. This is beautiful.
你在哪里得到这个？
Where did you get this?
这是日本人。
It's Japanese.
有一天我会把它挂在墙上。
One of these days I'm gonna hang it on my wall.
你充满了惊喜不是吗？
You're full of surprises aren't ya?
[Over P.A.] 巴黎和奥斯陆正在35号门的最后登船过程中。
[Over P.A.] Paris and Oslo is in its final boarding process at gate 35.
当地航班21：现在在22号登机口进入东京。
Local flight 21: Non stop into Tokyo now boarding at gate 22.
很荣幸成为您的客人。
It is an honor to be your guest.
荣誉是我们的，Yamada san。
The honor is ours, Yamada san.
我很感谢你寄给我日本的信。
I'm grateful for the letter you sent me to Japan.
我们有坏消息，Yamada san。
We have bad news, Yamada san.
但我们稍后会谈。
But we'll talk later.
嗨！ 怎么了？
Hi! What's wrong?
我要打破约会。 他们给了我下班的工作。
I gotta break our date. They gave me off-duty work.
那没问题。
That's OK.
你还好吗？
Are you alright?
听。 我得把Case推回去。 我以后会打电话给你好吗？
Listen. I gotta drive Case back. I'll call you later OK?
当然。
Sure.
再见。
Bye.
嘿!
Hey!
克里斯蒂！
Christie!
比利？ 你到底在哪里为基督的缘故！
Billy? Where in the hell are you for christ sakes!
你怎么了？ 阻止比利..
What's the matter with you?║Stop it Billy..
只是我感觉很奇怪。
It's just that I'm feeling really weird.
刚睡觉 我会在早上到那儿。
Just go to sleep. And I'll be there by morning.
没关系。 我没事儿的。
Never mind. I'll be OK.
你只需照顾好自己。
You just take care of yourself.
王八蛋。
Son of a bitch.
可恶。
God dammit.
什么..
What the..
你妈妈..我会杀了你。 你这个婊子的儿子！
You mother.. I'll kill you. You son of a bitch!
我勒个去..
What the hell..
什么..
What the..
不，不..
No. No..
不谢谢。 不，不。请。
No. Please. No. No. Please.
请。 哦。 神。
Please. Oh. God.
比利，我觉得我有点不对劲。
Billy, I think there's something wrong with me.
我甚至可以在它们发生之前感知它们。
I can sense things before they even happen.
我在公寓里找到了东西。
I find things in the apartment.
我甚至不知道他们来自哪里。
And I don't even know where they came from.
看这个。
Look at this.
耶稣！
Jesus!
你是怎么做到的？
How did you get that?
我不记得。
I don't remember.
你不记得是什么意思？
What do you mean you don't remember?
我的意思是我不记得了。
I mean I don't remember.
我一片空白。 用了几个小时。 也许更长。
I go blank. For hours. Maybe even longer.
我觉得有人让我做事。
I feel like there's somebody making me do things.
我不想做的事情。
Things that I don't wanna do.
然后做点什么吧。
Then do something about it.
亲爱的，我不知道该怎么办。
Honey, I don't know what to do.
我会帮助你的心上人。
I'll help you sweetheart.
医学上你是一个非常健康的年轻女性。
Medically you're a very fit young woman.
没有任何大脑异常的证据。
No evidence of any abnormality in the brain.
没有肿瘤。
No tumor.
你有一颗坚强的心。
You have a strong heart.
你的饮食比平均水平要好。
Your diet is better than average.
当然，你处于严重的压力之下。
You are under severe stress of course.
但除此之外，你看过的精神科医生博兰说：
But otherwise, doctor Boland, the psychiatrist you saw, says -
说没有什么不寻常的。
Says there's nothing out of the ordinary.
除了您特别的额外感官知觉。
Aside from your exceptional extra sensory perception.
而你的日本文化占领了。
And your pre-occupation with Japanese culture.
没有坏处。
No harm in that.
劳驾？
Excuse me?
你见过军官Secord吗？
Have you seen officer Secord?
不，我没有。
No I haven't.
哦，我们只会看看是谁让我了解它。
Oh well, we'll just see who put me up to it.
那么我们和你一起去吗？
So are we going with you?
哎呀..
Heck yes..
我想去一辆警车。
I wanna go in a police car.
好吧..
Well good..
我可以戴警笛和灯吗？
Can I put on the siren and the lights?
哦，我会明白的。
Oh I'll get it.
你们只是坐在那里
You guys just sit there.
这可能是谁？ 这太疯狂了。
Who could this be? This is crazy.
啊，你好。 来吧。我们可以使用更多的毛巾。
Oh hi. Come on in. We could use some more towels.
哦，它很热。 别拉我..
Ooh it's hot. Don't pull me..
这感觉很好。 我们一直很开心..
This feels good. We've been having fun..
她是谁？
Who's she?
我不知道。 但没关系。
I don't know. But it's alright.
你最好看自己的大个子！
You better watch yourself big man!
这到底是什么地方？
What the hell kind of place is this?
打它婊子！
Beat it bitch!
到底是怎么回事？
What's going on?
哎呀..
Jeez..
来吧孩子。 婊子的儿子全是你的。
Go ahead kid. The son of bitch is all yours.
哦，让我们分开..
Oh let's split..
不，我想看。
No. I wanna watch.
这家伙是个真正的混蛋。
This guy is a real jerk.
男孩。 你说的。
Boy. You said it.
让我们离开这里。
Let's get outta here.
她对他做了什么？
What is she doing to him?
我不知道。 但这个混蛋似乎很享受它不是吗？
I don't know. But the bastard seems to be enjoying it doesn't he?
当然可以。
Sure is.
嘿。 他出什么事了？
Hey. What's the matter with him?
没有！ 你在做什么？
No! What are you doing?
没有！
No!
克里斯蒂？
Christie?
你到底去了哪里？ 我到处寻找你。
Where the hell have you been? I looked everywhere for you.
克里斯蒂？
Christie?
到底是怎么回事？ 你去哪儿了？
What is going on? Where have you been?
我不知道。
I don't know.
你必须知道。 你从中午开始走了。
You gotta know. You've been gone since noon.
比利，我不在乎这些医生说的话。
Billy, I don't care what these doctors say.
我有点不对劲。
There's something wrong with me.
我试着去打它。
I try to fight it.
但我甚至不记得是什么。
But I can't even remember what.
或者为什么。
Or why.
有人，比利。
There's somebody, Billy.
我有时会在房间里感受到它。 听我说。
I can feel it in the room some times. Hear me.
听。 在亚洲分部有一名军官 -
Listen. There's an officer in the Asiatic division -
他告诉我，当地日本人的这个家伙发誓说。
He told me there's this guy downtown the local Japanese swear by.
为了您的信息，比利 -
For your information, Billy -
我不相信恶魔，鬼魂，精神或任何这类东西。
I don't believe in demons, ghosts, spirits, or any of that kind of stuff.
那我也不是。
Well neither do I.
但是当你空白时。 我们不知道该相信什么？
But when you blank out. We don't know what to believe in do we?
比利，我认为这不是一个好主意。
Billy, I don't think this is such a good idea.
你好。
Hello.
你好。 我叫Billy Secord。 我们通了电话。
Hi. My name is Billy Secord. We spoke on the phone.
哦，是的。 你是预期的。 你能跟我走吗？
Oh yes. You are expected. Would you follow me?
来你是明智的。 哦，年轻人。
It is wise of you to come. Oh young ones.
他现在在这里..
He is here now..
我可以告诉你更多。
I can tell you much more.
来。
Come.
跟着我。
Follow me.
肯定击败洛基恐怖图片展..
Sure beats the Rocky Horror Picture Show..
给他一个机会。
Give him a chance.
这些是必要的。
These are necessary.
如果精神变得生气。
In case the spirit becomes angry.
难道他甚至不会问我问题是什么？
Isn't he even gonna ask me what the problem is?
放轻松。
Just relax.
[诵经]
[Chanting]
亲爱的，别担心。 我会在这里
Don't worry sweetheart. I'll be right here.
[诵经]
[Chanting]
他在你吗？
Is he in you?
恩，他是。
Yes.. He is.
他希望你停下来！
And he wants you to stop!
你是谁？
Who are you?
[说日语]
[Speaking Japanese]
哦，我的上帝。
Oh my god.
也许我们最好停下来。
Maybe we better stop.
不，你完成了。
No. You finish it.
摆脱婊子的儿子。
Get rid of the son of a bitch.
我..我不知道有什么不对..
I.. I don't know what is wrong..
[诵经]
[Chanting]
[说日语]
[Speaking Japanese]
你在做什么？
What are you doing?
我必须服从精神。 他希望我把她剪掉。
I must obey the spirit. He wishes me to cut her loose.
没有！
No!
不，不，不。 停止。
No, no, don't. Stop.
请原谅他。 傻瓜不知道他犯了什么可怕的错误。
Please forgive him. The fool does not know what a terrible mistake he's making.
帮我！
Help me!
哦，比利。 帮我！
Oh Billy. Help me!
我害怕！
I'm scared!
你个笨蛋！
You fool!
你不能阻止我！
You cannot stop me!
我是忍者！
I am a ninja!
没有人，没有什么可以阻止我！
No one, nothing can stop me!
他已经去了。
He is gone.
你确定吗？
Are you sure?
他自己累了。
He's tired himself.
但他会回来。
But he will return.
什么时候？
When?
我不能说。
I cannot say.
我想知道他是谁。
I wanna know who he is.
我不能告诉你了。
I cannot tell you any more.
我听说过“忍者”。
I heard "ninja".
我想知道到底是怎么回事。
I wanna know what the hell that is.
你真好..你不太了解。
It is better you.. You not know too much.
为了你自己。
For your own sake.
你告诉我，你这个老混蛋。 或者我现在要打败你。
You tell me, you old bastard. Or I'm gonna bust you right now.
她被一个黑人忍者附身。
She is possessed by a black ninja.
拥有九手切割的所有力量。
With all the powers of the nine hand cutting.
什么都做不了。
Nothing can be done.
我告诉你她会完全......
I tell you she will be totally..
不要告诉我什么都做不了！
Don't tell me nothing can be done!
我希望你能帮助她！
I want you to help her!
抱歉。 我不能。
Sorry. I cannot.
有一件事......
There is one thing..
什么？
What?
在日本的鹰山。
In the Eagle Mountain in Japan.
一种可以摧毁他的力量。
The very one power that can destroy him.
日本..
Japan..
只有忍者才能摧毁忍者。
Only a ninja can destroy a ninja.
冻结！
Freeze!
嘿! 劳驾。
Hey! Excuse me.
你是谁？
Who are you?
我们可以帮你吗？
Can we help you?
你怎么进来的？
How'd you get in here?
是吗？
Yeah?
[说日语]
[Speaking Japanese]
所以你要告诉我发生了什么事吗？
So are you gonna tell me what happened?
他催眠了你就是这样。
He hypnotized you that's all.
那么为什么所有的瘀伤呢？
So why all the bruises?
来吧比利。 你可以告诉我。
Come on Billy. You can tell me.
我不认为他知道他在做什么。
I don't think he knew what he was doing.
这家伙可能是假的。
The guy's probably a fake.
有些东西你没告诉我。
There's something you're not telling me.
怎么样了？
How's it going?
克里斯蒂？
Christie?
对不起。 你好。
I'm sorry. Hi.
马蒂温斯洛 匹克威克中士 -
Marty Winslow. Sergeant Pickwick -
这是克里斯蒂。
This is Christie.
我知道这位女士很漂亮 -
I know the lady's beautiful -
但不要忘记葬礼。
But don't forget the funeral.
四点半。 克拉克市公墓。
Four thirty. Clark City Cemetery.
是啊。 我会努力做到的。
Yeah. I'll try and make it.
有什么新事吗？
Anything new?
没有。 只是猜测杀人事件与此有关 -
Nothing. Just speculation the killings are linked to that -
上周我们在高尔夫球场浪费了专业刺客。
professional assassin we wasted at the golf course last week.
你找到的那个僵硬 -
That stiff you found -
它被从太平间偷走了。
It was stolen out of the morgue.
现在，负责人认为这是一项专业工作 -
Now the chief believes it's a professional job -
某种日本黑手党或某种东西。
Some sort of Japanese mafia or something.
是啊。 所以要小心。
Yeah. So be careful.
四点半见。
See you at four thirty.
不，你没有。 不是了。
No you don't. Not again.
该死的你！
Damn you!
别管我！
Just leave me alone!
停下来！
Stop it!
没有！
No!
♪♪
♪ ♪
♪我一直梦见你♪
♪ I dream about you all the time ♪
♪我想不出别的♪
♪ I can't think about nothing else ♪
没有！
No!
拿去！
Nooo!
我们一起分享大卫的诗篇。 诗篇23。
And we share together the psalm of David. Psalm 23.
主是我的牧羊人。 我不想要。
The lord is my shepherd. I shall not want.
他让我躺在绿色的牧场上。
He makes me lie down in green pastures.
他带领我在安静的水域旁边。
He leads me beside quiet waters.
他恢复了我的灵魂。
He restores my soul.
为了他的名，他引导我走在正义的道路上。
He guides me in the paths of righteousness for his name's sake.
即使我走过死亡阴影的山谷
Even though I walk through the valley of the shadow of death
我不会因为你而害怕邪恶。
I will fear no evil for thou art with me.
你的杖和你的员工他们安慰我。
Thy rod and thy staff they comfort me.
在我的敌人面前，你在我面前准备了一张桌子。
Thou has prepared a table before me in the presence of mine enemies.
你用油涂抹了我的头。
Thou has anointed my head with oil.
我的杯子溢出来了。
My cup overflows.
当然，善良和慈爱将伴随着我生命中的每一天。
Surely goodness and loving kindness will follow me all of the days of my life.
我将永远住在主的家里。
And I will dwell in the house of the lord forever.
地球是主和它所包含的一切。
The earth is the lord's and all it contains.
处于戒备。 敬礼。
On Guard. Salute.
学员。
Cadets.
哦，我的上帝！
Oh my god!
下来！
Get down!
来吧。 打开那个行李箱。
Come on. Open that trunk.
给我一根接力棒。 我也是。 我们走吧。
Give me a baton. Me too. Let's go.
来吧。
Come on.
拿着它！ 他在这儿！
Hold it! He's over here!
把他吹走！
Blow him away!
来吧！
Come on up here!
过来这里 让他拥有它！
Come over here. Let him have it!
在那边见他？
See him over there?
冻结！ 拿着它！
Freeze!║Hold it!
传播他们！
Spread 'em!
我来和他谈谈
Let me talk to him.
移动它。
Move it.
我不得不问...... - 我在等你。
I have to ask..║- I was waiting for you.
你了解我？
You know me?
你知道剑在哪里吗？
You know where the sword is?
也许..
Maybe..
不要犹豫 -
Do not hesitate -
我是从日本来复仇的。
I have come from Japan to revenge.
我知道应该做些什么。
I know what should be done.
你是忍者？
You're a ninja?
没关系。
It doesn't matter.
去拿女孩和剑 -
Go and get the girl and the sword -
带他们去古庙。
And take them to the old temple.
在山上。
On the hill.
等等我。
Wait for me.
别担心。
Don't worry.
嘿。 嘿查理..
Hey. Hey Charlie..
嘿这里发生了什么？
Hey what's going on here?
他们只是在睡觉。
They are only sleeping.
嘿!
Hey!
比利，你害怕我。
Billy you scared me.
天哪，我很高兴你在这里..
God, I'm so glad you're here..
别动。
Don't move.
你在做什么？
What are you doing?
我说只是不动。
I said just don't move.
他们都死了克里斯蒂..
They're all dead Christie..
你杀了他们。
You killed them.
我看到了一切。
I saw everything.
我没有杀死任何人..
I haven't killed anybody..
听我说 -
Listen to me -
这里有一个来自日本的男人。
There's a man here from Japan.
一个忍者。
A ninja.
我们要去山上那座古老的寺庙见他。
We're gonna go meet him at that old temple on the hill.
他会帮助你。
And he is going to help you.
我可以......  - 别动！
I can.. - Don't move!
我永远无法做任何伤害你的事情......
I could never do anything to hurt you..
天哪，我希望这是真的。
Oh god I hope that's true.
把手伸到你面前。
Put your hands out in front of you.
但比利..
But Billy..
把手伸到你面前！
Put your hands out in front of you!
我爱你..
I love you..
克里斯蒂不......
Christie no..
克里斯蒂没有。
Christie no.
克里斯蒂！
Christie!!
快醒来。 来吧。 来吧。
Wake up now. Come on. Come on.
该死的！
Damn!
[说日语]
[Speaking Japanese]
你是忍者。
You're the ninja.
你可以帮助我？
You can help me?
是。
Yes.
只有忍者可以摧毁一个忍者才真的吗？
Is it true that only a ninja can destroy a ninja?
是真的。
It's true.
请帮帮我。 我必须摆脱他。
Help me please. I must get rid of him.
你知道我必须做什么吗？
Do you know what I must do?
做你需要的。 我不想伤害别人。
Do what you have to. I don't wanna hurt anyone else.
这对你来说可能很危险。
It might be dangerous for you.
我会死吗？
Will I die?
如果灵魂离开你，那就不是了。
Not if the spirit leaves you.
并回到他的身体。
And returns to his body.
然后我会毁了他。
Then I will destroy him.
你会安全的。
And you will be safe.
如果没有 -
And if it doesn't -
你会害死我。
You'll kill me.
不好了..
Oh no..
来吧克里斯蒂。
Come on Christie.
来吧。
Come on.
比利？
Billy?
我想我现在好了..
I think I'm gonna be alright now..
哦，我爱你！
Oh I love you!
我爱你。
I love you.
比利等。
Billy wait.
克里斯蒂不！
Christie no!
现在结束了。
It's over now.